[{"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121116pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "Can we say that for certain or could it be that there were some protesters and there was also a planned attack because it was September the 11th?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "One of the saddest aspects of this entire mess was that Petraeus was one of our best generals in recent years.", "docId": "121116pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "But where do you position him in terms of his legacy as a general?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "Yes, pretty much.", "docId": "121116pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "Was that your reading of it?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "I think he'll be remembered a lot like Matthew Ridgway, which is to say pretty much not at all except by the experts.", "docId": "121116pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "Where do you think General Petraeus ranks as a general, say, in the last hundred years?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "I -- I had introduced Paula, actually, to my book editor.", "docId": "121116pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "Did the Paula Broadwell book that came out about General Petraeus, did you like that as a historian?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "What I think is that spies are probably like soldiers.", "docId": "121116pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "What do you think of that?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "It's going to resolve itself when Hamas cease firing rockets at millions of innocent Israeli civilians.", "docId": "121116pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "How is this going to resolve itself?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "We are certainly keeping that option open.", "docId": "121116pmt", "aSentId": 154, "question": "Are you preparing for a ground invasion?", "qSentId": 153}, {"answer": "No, and I think the Gazans should make a decision about the type of government they want.", "docId": "121116pmt", "aSentId": 159, "question": "Would you like to live on the Gaza Strip?", "qSentId": 158}, {"answer": "Well, the crossings have been open.", "docId": "121116pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "The international community has got to somehow offer the people in Gaza more hope, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "Well, we preferred to look at Egyptian deeds rather than words.", "docId": "121116pmt", "aSentId": 186, "question": "What did you make of that?", "qSentId": 185}, {"answer": "Well, we're going to take any measures necessary to stop the aggression against the civilians.", "docId": "121116pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "Is your intention at the same time to continue targeting Hamas leaders and to continue, if you can, killing them?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "The way to break through it would be for the Palestinians to accept that there is a state of Israel, which is permanent and legitimate, and to sit down with us at the negotiating table to negotiate all the outstanding issues -- whether it'd be borders, refugees, Jerusalem, security, recognition.", "docId": "121116pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "What is the way to break through this?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "That's not only disingenuous, but it's very misleading and it has very little to do with the truth.", "docId": "121116pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "What is your reaction?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "No, we don't have control over Hamas.", "docId": "121116pmt", "aSentId": 249, "question": "Does the PLO have any real control over Hamas?", "qSentId": 248}, {"answer": "No, because Hamas did acknowledge that should there be a negotiated settlement that's accepted by a referendum, by the Palestinian people, then they are quite willing to abide by it.", "docId": "121116pmt", "aSentId": 257, "question": "If you're an Israeli listening to this, it's saying, well, it's all very well you talking in about how to resolve this, but if you have no control whatsoever over the activities of Hamas, why should they trust you?", "qSentId": 256}, {"answer": "Well, I think the danger is that they both escalate as a result.", "docId": "121116pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "How do we get through the fact that both of them have pretty good arguments?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I think we have to accept that we're not going to kill our way to a solution here, that, in fact, in many cases the use of military force is counterproductive.", "docId": "121116pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "From a military point of view, is there anything that the Americans could be doing or pushing the Israelis to do to try and somehow come to a resolution that can work?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "Well, I agree with Alan that Israel certainly has a right to self-defense.", "docId": "121116pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "Who can bring that to them?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "Actually, in some ways, it made things more confusing.", "docId": "121116pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "Was that your reading?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "In some ways, I think Mark is right that it has gotten muddier.", "docId": "121116pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "I mean, depending again who you talk to -- there you have a top general saying it's just gotten a lot muddier, and that actually -- is this the danger when you have the need to keep stuff classified because you're going after certain groups you think may have done this, but sending people out like Ambassador Rice to spin a yarn that it may have been a video protest?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "And it is heartbreaking.", "docId": "121116pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "It's an absolute basket case there, isn't it?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "Well, I think I would like to go back to Alan's point, which is exactly right.", "docId": "121116pmt", "aSentId": 416, "question": "The Arab Spring fallout, what is your take on that?", "qSentId": 415}, {"answer": "Hi, Piers.", "docId": "121116pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know.", "docId": "121116pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "Can we expect anything to improve?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "I suppose the ones with the real problems are not the Democrats, because they've got back in.", "docId": "121116pmt", "aSentId": 446, "question": "They wouldn't lie to us, would they?", "qSentId": 445}, {"answer": "Well, I think they need to change their ideas rather than their people.", "docId": "121116pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "What do the Republicans do to try and reinvent themselves and make themselves more relevant, do you think?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "The big thing he has going for him is that he has four years that he doesn't have to worry about getting re-elected.", "docId": "121116pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "And what do you want him to do now that he has four more years?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "Well, I think he's been weak -- my son was a huge Obama supporter until Obama ordered that American's death with the drone.", "docId": "121116pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "Where do you think he's been weak and where does he need to be stronger?", "qSentId": 470}]